<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="simple_ans">
        <item>Android is an open-source,
            linux-based operating system that is used
            in mobiles, tablets, televisions etc.
        </item>
        <item>
            Andy Rubin.
        </item>
        <item>
           Following is a list of components of Android application architecture:\n\n

            Services: Used to perform background functionalities.\n\n
            Intent: Used to perform the inter connection between activities
                    and the data passing mechanism.\n\n
            Resource Externalization: strings and graphics.\n\n
            Notification: light, sound, icon, notification, dialog box and toast.\n\n
            Content Providers: It will share the data between applications.
        </item>
        <item>
            Aestro\n\n
            Blender\n\n
            Cupcake\n\n
            Donut\n\n
            Eclair\n\n
            Froyo\n\n
            Gingerbread\n\n
            Honeycomb\n\n
            Ice Cream Sandwitch\n\n
            Jelly Bean\n\n
            Kitkat\n\n
            Lollipop\n\n
            Marshmallow\n\n
            Nougat\n\n
            Oreo
        </item>
        <item>
            Open-source: It means no licence, distribution and development fee.\n\n

            Platform-independent: It supports windows, mac and linux platforms.\n\n

            Supports various technologies: It supports camera, bluetooth, wifi,
                         speech, EDGE etc. technologies.\n\n

            Highly optimized Virtual Machine: Android uses highly optimized virtual machine
                         for mobile devices, called DVM (Dalvik Virtual Machine).
        </item>
        <item>
            Yes, android app can be developed in C/C++ also using android NDK (Native Development Kit).
            It makes the performance faster. It should be used with android SDK.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            The core building blocks of android are:\n\n

                Activity\n\n
                View\n\n
                Intent\n\n
                Service\n\n
                Content Provider\n\n
                Fragment etc.
        </item>
        <item>
            Activity is like a frame or window in java that represents GUI.
            It represents one screen of android.
        </item>
        <item>
            There are 7 life-cycle methods of activity. They are as follows:\n\n

            onCreate()\n\n
            onStart()\n\n
            onResume()\n\n
            onPause()\n\n
            onStop()\n\n
            onRestart()\n\n
            onDestroy()
        </item>
        <item>
            It is a kind of message or information that is passed to the components.
            It is used to launch an activity, display a web page, send sms, send email etc.
            There are two types of intents in android:\n\n

            Implicit Intent\n\n
            Explicit Intent\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Implicit intent is used to invoke the system components.
        </item>
        <item>
            Explicit intent is used to invoke the activity class.
        </item>
        <item>
            Intent i = new Intent(getApplicationContext(), ActivityTwo.class);\n
            startActivity(i);
        </item>
        <item>
            A service is a component that runs in the background. It is used to play music,
            handle network transaction etc.
        </item>
        <item>
            SQLite: An opensource and lightweight relational database for mobile devices.
        </item>
        <item>
            AAPT is an acronym for android asset packaging tool. It handles the packaging process.
        </item>
        <item>
            Content providers are used to share information between android applications.
        </item>
        <item>
            Fragment is a part of Activity. By the help of fragments, we can display multiple screens
            on one activity.
        </item>
        <item>
            ADB stands for Android Debug Bridge. It is a command line tool that is used to communicate
            with the emulator instance.
        </item>
        <item>
            NDK stands for Native Development Kit. By using NDK, you can develop a part of app using
            native language such as C/C++ to boost the performance.
        </item>
        <item>
            ANR stands for Application Not Responding. It is a dialog box that appears if the application
            is no longer responding.
        </item>
        <item>
            The Google Android SDK is a toolset which is used by developers to write apps on Android
            enabled devices. It contains a graphical interface that emulates an Android driven handheld
            environment and allow them to test and debug their codes.
        </item>
        <item>
            APK is a short form stands for Android Packaging Key. It is a compressed key with classes,
            UI's, supportive assets and manifest. All files are compressed to a single file is called APK.
        </item>
        <item>
            Android applications are written by using the java (Android SDK) and C/C++ (Android NDK).
        </item>
        <item>
            ADT stands for Android Development Tool. It is used to develop the applications and test
            the applications.
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>