<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="simple_ans">
        <item>Android is an open-source,
            linux-based operating system that is used
            in mobiles, tablets, televisions etc.
        </item>
        <item>
            Andy Rubin.
        </item>
        <item>
           Following is a list of components of Android application architecture:

            Services: Used to perform background functionalities.
            Intent: Used to perform the inter connection between activities
                    and the data passing mechanism.
            Resource Externalization: strings and graphics.
            Notification: light, sound, icon, notification, dialog box and toast.
            Content Providers: It will share the data between applications.
        </item>
        <item>
            Aestro
            Blender
            Cupcake
            Donut
            Eclair
            Froyo
            Gingerbread
            Honycomb
            Ice Cream Sandwitch
            Jelly Bean
            Kitkat
            Lollipop
            Marshmallow
            Nougat
            Oreo
        </item>
        <item>
            Open-source: It means no licence, distribution and development fee.

            Platform-independent: It supports windows, mac and linux platforms.

            Supports various technologies: It supports camera, bluetooth, wifi,
                         speech, EDGE etc. technologies.

            Highly optimized Virtual Machine: Android uses highly optimized virtual machine
                         for mobile devices, called DVM (Dalvik Virtual Machine).
        </item>
        <item>
            Yes, android app can be developed in C/C++ also using android NDK (Native Development Kit).
            It makes the performance faster. It should be used with android SDK.
        </item>
        <item>
            The core building blocks of android are:

                Activity
                View
                Intent
                Service
                Content Provider
                Fragment etc.
        </item>
        <item>
            Activity is like a frame or window in java that represents GUI.
            It represents one screen of android.
        </item>
        <item>
            There are 7 life-cycle methods of activity. They are as follows:

            onCreate()
            onStart()
            onResume()
            onPause()
            onStop()
            onRestart()
            onDestroy()
        </item>
        <item>
            It is a kind of message or information that is passed to the components.
            It is used to launch an activity, display a web page, send sms, send email etc.
            There are two types of intents in android:

            Implicit Intent
            Explicit Intent
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>